in this tutorial we'll be going over an
在本教程中，我们将介绍一个
example of what can be created using the
可以使用
spiral tool in inkscape and to show you
Inkscape中的螺旋工具，并向您展示
what I mean I have this simple spiral
我的意思是我有一个简单的螺旋
path that I started off with and I was
我开始的那条路，我是
able to use it to construct this rolled
能够用它来建造这个卷曲
sheet of paper icon that you could see
你可以看到的一张纸图标
here and I will be demonstrating how to
在这里，我将演示如何
create this entire thing so let me come
创造了这整件事，让我来吧
over here into a new document and we
在这里变成一份新的文件，我们
will get started so the first thing I'm
将会开始，所以我第一件事就是
going to do is grab my spiral tool which
我要做的就是抓起我的螺旋工具
is located over here and the tool
位于这里，而该工具
settings I want to use I already have
我想使用的设置我已经有了
inputed into my input boxes here so go
已输入到我的输入框中，请继续
ahead and pause the video and type in
向前，暂停视频，然后键入
these values into each of these three
将这些值转化为这三个值中的每个
boxes here we want 2.9 2.0 and
这里的盒子我们想要2.9和2.0
0.550 and once you do that you'll be
0.550，一旦你做到了，你就会成为
good to get started so now what I will
很高兴开始，所以现在我要做的是
do is I will hold the control key and
我要做的就是按住控制键
click and drag to the right to create a
单击并向右拖动以创建
spiral and the way that I want this
螺旋和我想要的方式
spiral positioned I want the tail of the
螺旋形的位置我想要尾巴
Spiral on the right hand side I want
我想要右手边的螺旋形
that to rest on the horizontal plane so
在水平面上休息，所以
that it's going up vertically like that
它是那样垂直上升的
we don't want it offc Center like that
我们不想让它像那样离开中心
we want it placed just like that and
我们想把它放在那样的位置上
that's the result we're looking for and
这就是我们想要的结果
now I'm going to convert this to a path
现在，我将把它转换成一条路径
so I'll come up here to where it says
所以我会到上面写着的地方
path and I will go to object to path and
PATH和我将去反对PATH和
I'm going to grab my selection tool and
我要拿起我的选择工具
I'm going to flip this vertically by
我要把这个垂直地翻过来
pressing this button right here that
按下这里的按钮，就是
says flip uh object vertically or you
说垂直翻转呃物体或者你
could just press the letter V on your
可以只在你的电脑上按下字母V吗
keyboard and that works as well and I'm
键盘和键盘工作得很好，我
going to zoom in on this and I'm going
我要把这个放大，然后我要
to click on it again to get the rotation
再次单击它以获得旋转
handles I'm going to rotate this around
把手我要把这个旋转一下
a little bit just so that this tail
一点就是为了让这条尾巴
right here is not too far up we don't
就在这里，不是很高，我们不
want that too far up like that we want
想要像那样飞得太高我们想要
this down a little bit and that looks a
这个稍微往下一点，这看起来是
lot better so what I'm going to do now
好多了，所以我现在要做的
is first of all come up here to the tool
首先是到这个工具上来
settings menu if you hover your cursor
如果将光标悬停在屏幕上，则会显示设置菜单
over this first of four icons right here
在这里的四个图标中的第一个
it'll say when scaling objects scale the
它会显示当缩放对象时缩放
stroke width by the same proportion make
笔划宽度按相同比例制作
sure you have that turned off right now
当然，你现在已经把它关掉了
we want that disabled and once we do
我们想让它失灵，一旦我们这样做了
that I'm going to come back over here to
我要回到这里来
my object click on it again to get back
我的对象再次点击它以返回
to my scaling handles and I'm going to
到我的伸缩手柄上，我要
take this bottom Arrow icon right here
把这个底部箭头图标放在这里
and just scale this up like that so we
就像这样扩大规模，这样我们就可以
have this distorted effect as you can
尽可能地让这种扭曲的效果
see here and once we've done that I'm
看这里，一旦我们做完那个，我就
just going to click on it again I'm
只需再次点击它，我就
going to rotate this a little bit more
我要把这个旋转得更多一点
I'm not quite happy with how that looks
我对它的样子不太满意
all right that looks a lot better and
好的，看起来好多了，而且
now I'm going to open up the fill and
现在我要打开填充物
stroke menu so come over here to where
中风菜单，请到这里来
it says path or No Object and go to fill
它显示路径或无对象，然后转到填充
and stroke and the menu should open up
和笔划，菜单应该会打开
over here on your right hand side of
在你的右手边
your screen I'm going to select the
您的屏幕我将选择
stroke style Tab and I want to change
笔划样式选项卡和我想要更改
the width of the stroke from one pixel
从一个像素开始的笔划宽度
to five pixel
到5个像素
pixels and I want to make the caps
Pixels和我想要制作帽子
rounded as well and then I want to come
也很圆润，然后我想去
down here and bring the opacity of this
把这个不透明的东西带到这里
down in half this is just going to make
降到一半，这将使
it easier for us to see what we're
我们更容易看清我们是什么
working with as we move
在我们移动的同时使用
forward so we now have the top portion
向前看，我们现在得到了顶部
design so what I'm going to do is I'm
所以我要做的就是
going to right click this and go to
要右键单击此选项并转到
duplicate and I'm going to hold the
复制件，我要拿着
control key and move this down here like
按住Ctrl键，然后像这样向下移动
this this is going to represent the top
这个，这将代表顶端
of the roll of paper and this is going
一卷纸，这就是
to represent the bottom if I could show
来代表底部，如果我能展示
show you what I mean here this is the
让你看看我在这里的意思这是
shape we're starting off with and this
我们开始的形状和这个
is what we're putting it we're putting
就是我们所说的，我们所说的
it down there like that and now what I
它就在那里，现在我
will do is let me click off of that to
我要做的就是让我点击这个按钮
deselect it I'm going to turn on
取消选择它，我要打开它
snapping I'm going to come over here to
抓拍我要到这里来
this magnet icon and enable that let me
这个磁铁图标和启用让我
expand this menu and we don't want
展开此菜单，我们不希望
advanced mode if you're in advanced mode
高级模式(如果您处于高级模式
just come over here to where it says
只要到上面写着的地方来
reset to simple snapping mode and the
重置为简单捕捉模式，并且
two options we want enabled in simple
我们希望在Simple中启用两个选项
mode are bounding boxes and nodes and
模式是边界框和节点，以及
we're going to keep alignment turned off
我们将保持对齐关闭
so now I'm going to grab my bezier pen
所以现在我要拿起我的贝塞尔钢笔
which is located over here or the pen
哪个在这里，哪个在笔
tool as it's called and I'm going to
它被称为工具，我要
come over here and I'm going to snap to
到这里来，我要抓紧了
the left side of this spiral and let me
这个螺旋的左边，让我
zoom out I'm going to bring the line
拉近我要把这条线
straight down I'm going to hold my
直截了当地说，我要拿着我的
control key to lock it onto the vertical
Ctrl键将其锁定在垂直方向上
axis and then snap to the left edge of
轴，然后捕捉到的左边缘
the other shape like that and press
另一个像那样的形状，然后按下
enter and now we want to give this
进入，现在我们要给出这个
stroke the same style so let me change
划动同样的风格，让我改变
this to five pixels and I'll make these
把这个调到五个像素，我会把这些
caps arounded as well and I'll bring
帽子也围了起来，我会带上
down the opacity of that in half and you
把它的不透明度减半，你就会
can see why I'm turning down the opacity
我明白为什么我要把不透明调低
I want to be able to see where this line
我想看看这条线在哪里
lines up with the other path with the
与另一条路径对齐
spiral path I want to make sure
螺旋路径，我想确保
everything there is nice and lined up
那里的一切都很好，排成了一排
and having partial opacity makes it easy
而部分不透明让它变得很容易
to see through these objects while you
当你看到这些物体的时候
do that so now let's create another line
这样做，现在让我们创建另一行
going over here let's connect this top
过来，让我们把这件上衣连接起来
part to this bottom part over here I'm
在这下面的部分我是
going to hold control bring this
控制住，把这个拿来
straight down and then snap it onto the
笔直往下，然后把它扣在
path right there and press enter to
PATH就在那里，然后按Enter键
create the line I'm going to make the
创建我要制作的线条
width five pixels make the Caps rounded
宽度五个像素使大写字母四舍五入
and bring the opacity down in half like
把不透明度降低一半，就像
that and now we have the right side in
现在我们有了正确的一方
place okay so I'll just zoom in to make
位置没问题，这样我就可以放大来制作
sure everything looks correct here we
当然，这里的一切看起来都很正常
want this nice and smooth we don't want
我们不想要这样美好而顺畅的生活
anything off
任何打折的东西
center and now I'm going to do the same
现在我也要做同样的事
thing over here let me snap to this
这里的东西，让我抓住这个
piece bring this straight down by
把这个直接拿下来
holding the control key snap to the
按住Ctrl键捕捉到
bottom part click again and press enter
底部再次单击，然后按Enter键
I'm going to make this five
我要把这个加到五个
pixels make the caps rounded bring the
像素使大写字母变圆，带来
opacity down and I'll do the same thing
降低透明度，我也会做同样的事情
over here I'll snap to the right Edge
在这里，我将捕捉到右侧边缘
bring the line straight down by holding
握住绳子，把绳子拉下来
control there we go let me change the
控制在那里我们走让我改变
style of this one as
此版本的样式为
well and it's starting to come together
嗯，它开始走到一起了
as you can see we now have to get rid of
如你所见，我们现在必须摆脱
this bottom piece down here so uh
下面的这一块，所以呢
there's various ways we can get rid of
我们有多种方法可以摆脱
this bottom piece down here the way that
下面的这一块是这样的
I'm going to do this is I'm going to
我要这么做是因为我要
grab my select tool I'm going to enable
抓起我的选择工具，我要启用
the ruler on my canvas by pressing
按下画布上的尺子
controlr on the keyboard if you're using
如果您正在使用键盘上的Controlr
Mac it would be command R so I'm going
麦克，这是R号指挥部，所以我要走了
to press command R and now we have the
按下命令R，现在我们有
ruler and I'm going to come up here to
统治者和我要到这里来
the horizontal ruler and click and drag
水平标尺并单击并拖动
to pull a guide down and I'm going to
把导游拉下来，我要
snap that guide right where the end
将导轨固定在末端位置
point of this vertical line is and now
这条垂直线的点是和现在
I'm going to select this path right here
我要在这里选择这条路
and I will grab my nodes tool and I will
我会拿起我的节点工具我会
double click right there to add a new
在那里双击以添加新的
node and I'll make sure that Noe is
诺德和我会确保诺伊
selected and I want to come up here to
被选中了，我想来这里
where it says uh not join selected we
上面写着，呃，没有加入选定的我们
want this one right here break path at
想要这个就在这里中断路径在
selected nodes and that's going to break
选定的节点，这将中断
that up into separate
分成不同的部分
pieces and now I'm going to grab my
现在我要拿起我的
select tool I'll go to path and I will
选择工具我将转到路径，然后我将
select break
选择中断
apart deselect it by clicking off onto
通过单击关闭来取消选择该选项
the canvas and I'm going to take this
画布和我要拿着这个
piece and just press delete to get rid
然后只需按Delete键即可删除
of it and then I will get rid of the
然后我就会处理掉
guide I'll press I'll click on the guide
指南我会按下，我会点击指南
hover the cursor over it until it
将光标悬停在它上面，直到它
highlights red press the delete key to
突出显示红色，按Delete键即可
get rid of the guide and now I will get
把导游弄走，现在我要
rid of the ruler as well by holding uh
握住这个尺子也可以把它拿掉
command and pressing r or controlr if
命令并按r或Control，如果
you're on Windows or Linux so a lot of
您使用的是Windows或Linux，所以很多
this is in place now all we have to do
现在我们要做的就是
now is create these lines of text or
现在是创建这些文本行或
what are supposed to be lines of text
什么应该是文本行？
and then we'll fill this in with some
然后我们会在这里面填上一些
color so let me uh let me click on this
颜色，让我，呃，让我点击这个
object up here the original spiral path
物体在这里，原始的螺旋路径
I'm going to right click that and go to
我要右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate and I'll hold control and
复制，我会控制和控制
bring this straight down like this let's
像这样直接把它拿下来，让我们
turn off snapping now we don't need that
关闭捕捉，现在我们不需要该功能
anymore and I just want to I just want
我只想我只想我只想
to take this segment right here and use
将这个片段放在这里并使用
it that so let me grab the rectangle
是吗？让我拿一下那个长方形
tool and I'll click and drag and create
工具，我将点击并拖动并创建
a rectangle over that portion of the
该部分上的一个矩形。
Spiral right there we just want to take
就在那里，我们只想要
this selection and then I'll select both
这个选项，然后我会同时选择这两个
of those and I will go to path and
我会走到小路上
select cut path and that should break it
选择切割路径，这应该会中断它
up into separate pieces and now we can
分成不同的部分，现在我们可以
just take this piece right here and get
只要把这块拿在这里，就可以
rid of that and get rid of this piece
扔掉那个，扔掉这块
right here as well and let me move this
就在这里，让我把这个搬开
up I'm going to hold control while doing
向上，我要在做的时候保持控制
this so that we lock it onto the
这样我们就可以把它锁在
vertical axis and I'm going to duplicate
垂直轴，我要复制
this instead of right clicking and going
这不是用鼠标右键点击即走
to duplicate I'm just going to press
要复制，我只需按下
contrl D or command D if you're on Mac
如果您在Mac上，请按Ctrl D或Command D
and then I'll take this duplicate copy
然后我要这份复印件
and move that down and I'm going to
把它往下移，我要
repeat this I'm going to select both of
重复这一点，我要选择这两个
these control D to duplicate bring them
这些控件D将它们复制到
down here and I'll do this maybe one
在这下面，我会做这个，也许是一个
more time bring these ones down
更多的时间把这些打倒
here and now we want to make sure that
此时此刻，我们希望确保
these lines are evenly spaced so let me
这些线是均匀分布的，所以让我
select all of them and I will open up my
把它们全部选中，我就会打开我的
aligned distribute menu you can access
您可以访问对齐的分发菜单
that by going to object and selecting
通过去反对和选择
aligned distribute I already have mine
对齐分发我已经有我的了
open over here in my dock dockable menu
在我的对接菜单中打开此处
so I'll just click on that and the
所以我只需点击它，然后
option I'm looking for over here where
我在这里寻找的选择在哪里？
it says distribute we want to choose
上面写着分配我们想要选择
this option right here that says even
就在这里，这个选项意味着
vertical gaps and when I click on
垂直间隙和当我单击
that it makes everything spaced apart
它让所有的东西都被隔开
evenly and what we could do now is I'm
我们现在能做的就是我
just going to adjust this a little bit
我要稍微调整一下这个
what we could do now is we can combine
我们现在能做的就是结合
all of these Strokes together so that
所有这些笔划都在一起，所以
this becomes one shape so I'm going to
这变成了一个形状，所以我要
select everything and I will go to path
选择所有内容，我将转到路径
and select combine
并选择合并
and once you do that you can come back
一旦你这样做了，你就可以回来了
over to your fill and stroke menu and we
转到您的填充和描边菜单，我们
can bring the opacity all the way up and
可以将不透明度提高到最高
if you want you can make the stroke
如果你愿意，你可以划一划
larger another way that you can make the
更大的另一种方法，可以使
stroke larger is that you can just scale
更大的笔划是，你可以只缩放
this down I'm going to hold control and
在这件事上，我要控制局面，
scale this down and since we have this
缩小规模，因为我们有这个
setting disabled as we scale the object
在我们缩放对象时禁用设置
the stroke size will stay the same so if
笔划大小将保持不变，因此如果
you want a heavier stroke you can scale
你想要一个可以伸缩的更重的笔划
this down like that and you could see
这样往下走，你就能看到
the result as it's happening and once
结果就像它正在发生的那样，一旦
you're happy with the thickness of the
你对它的厚度很满意
stroke let's enable this setting again
笔划，让我们再次启用此设置
so so that now we can enlarge this
所以现在我们可以把它放大
object without losing those
对象，但不会丢失
proportions and I'm actually going to
比例，我真的要
adjust that a little bit I don't want it
稍微调整一下，我不想要。
that
那
heavy okay that looks a little better so
重的，好的，看起来好一点，所以
all that's left now is to color this
现在剩下的就是给这个上色了
thing in so let me zoom in on this a
所以让我放大这张图
little bit and I'm going to come over
一点点，我就会过来
here to my stroke paint Tab and I'm
这是我的笔划绘制选项卡，我是
going to give this a dark blue color
我要把这个颜色改成深蓝色
I'll come over here to the original
我会到这里来看看原件
design you can see how I colored it here
你可以看到我是如何在这里给它上色的
this is I'm going to go for something
这是我要去做的事
similar right here I mean obviously you
就在这里，我的意思是很明显你
can color this however you'd like I'm
我可以随心所欲地给它上色
just going to go with this blue theme
我只想用这个蓝色的主题
I'll make this a little
我会把这个做得有点
darker and I want to fill in these empty
Darker和我想要填补这些空白
areas here using the paint bucket tool
此处使用画桶工具的区域
so let me grab the paint bucket tool and
所以让我拿起油漆桶工具
I'm going to click on this area right
我要右击这个区域
here to fill it in and I'm going to
在这里填写它，我要
change that color to something else oops
把那个颜色换成别的颜色。
that was the wrong thing let me press
那是错误的事情，让我按一下
control Z I want to choose the fill tab
Control Z我想选择填充选项卡
not the stroke paint tab there we go let
不是笔画的油漆标签，我们走吧
me make this a different
我让这一切变得不同
color I'll go with a lighter shade of
我想要浅一点的颜色。
blue and I'll come over here and fill
布鲁和我会到这里来填满
this in as well I'll make this a
我也要把这件事做成一个
I don't know why it's applying a stroke
我不知道它为什么要划一划
let me get rid of that there we go I'll
让我把它处理掉，我们走吧，我会的
take this and I'll make this one a
拿着这个，我就把这个做成一个
little
一点儿
darker maybe I'll put a little more blue
再暗一点，也许我会再加一点蓝色
in
在……里面
there and then I'll do this one more
然后我会再来一次
time I'll fill that one in and I'll make
时间到了，我会把它填进去，然后我会
this one the darkest of them all so let
这是他们中最黑暗的一个，所以让
me make it a little
我让它变得有点
darker and I'm actually going to make
Darker和我实际上要让
this stroke a little darker as well to
这一笔也稍微暗了一点
accommodate these uh other colors and
适应这些呃其他颜色和
once that's done we want to raise this
一旦完成，我们想要提出这个
to the top so I'm going to press this
到顶端，所以我要按这个
button over here that says raise to the
这里有一个按钮，上面写着升到
top we want that we want the stroke
上面我们想要我们想要划水
object on top of everything else on top
对象位于顶部的所有其他对象之上
of the fill objects and we could zoom
填充对象的大小，我们可以缩放
out and you can see we are finished so
出去，你可以看到我们完成了，所以
that's an example of what you can do
这就是你能做到的一个例子
using the spiral tool in inkscape if you
如果您使用Inkscape中的螺旋工具
found this lesson useful then consider
觉得这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how how I did in this video
就像我在这段视频中做的那样
we even have a private Community where
我们甚至有一个私人社区，在那里
you can ask questions and get help from
您可以通过以下方式提问并获得帮助
me anytime you want and best of all
任何你想要的时间我都可以，最棒的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
你不需要缴纳月费
just pay $17 one time and you're in for
只需一次性支付17美元，你就会面临
Life I'll have some information about
我会有一些关于生活的信息
that down below if you want to check
如果您想查看下面的内容
that out as always thanks for
一如既往的感谢你
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
观看